# Anna Barbera

DATA ANALYST

#### **Details**

Winston-Salem, NC, 27104 USA +1 (210) 956-9500 annacbarbera@gmail.com

#### Software

SQL

Python

Full Stack Data Visualizations

HTML/CSS

Flask

**JavaScript** 

GitHub & GitBash

Adobe Photoshop

Microsoft Office

Data Dashboards

DocShuttle

ByteScribe

### **Skills**

Python Libraries:

**Pandas** 

NumPy

Matplotlib

Sklern

SciPy

Anaconda

Beautiful Soup

Selenium

Mongoengine

Other Skills:

Predictive Modeling

Jupyter Notebooks

Tableau

Database Development

Machine Learning

Understanding of ORM

Libraries

**Creative Thinking** 

**Excellent Communication Skills** 

Strong Analytical Skills

**Project Management** 

## **Profile**

Ambitious contributor with a history of self-motivated success in a variety of roles. Expertise in client facing roles, remote employment, quality control, collaborative roles, and fast-paced workforce environments that require high levels of accuracy. Willing to relocate.

# **Employment History**

# Medical Transcriptionist, Your Second Office, LLC, Baton Rouge, LA

2016 - 2022

- Interpret and convert written and verbal information to data driven KPIs.
- Produce high volumes of daily deliverables from raw data.
- Execute fast turn-arounds for urgent deliverables.
- Maintain privacy and data security of deliverables.
- Expert ability to prioritize projects under constant deadlines.
- Execute proper flagging procedure for compromised files.
- Ensure accurate documentation and organization with regards to deliverables.
- Generate and organize a high number of sensitive documents in multiple company databases.
- Trained and mentored new hires.

## Business Manager, Rene Barbera, Tenor, LLC, International

JANUARY 2015 - DECEMBER 2018

- Maintain and organize business records and financial information.
- Process, organize, and prioritze incoming mail, including time-sensitive documents and contracts.
- Generate and distribute finanical spreadsheets.
- Copy writer.
- Design and produce social media content.
- Creative liason and content builder with public relations team, focusing on brand awareness and marketing campaigns.

## **Business Associate, Adecco Employment Agency**

- Verizon Wireless Call Center, quality control and processing customer contract activation and termination paperwork.
- American Eagle Outfitter's National Headquarters. Extract, organize, and manage data in computer databases; process customer service claims.
- Receptionist at Barrett Jaguar. Answer and manage multi-line phones, provide customer service, data entry, calendar management, MS office, maintaining a cheerful and helpful disposition.

More employment history available on request, which includes a history of full and part-time retail, customer service, and receptionist roles.

## **Education**

Data Science & Analytics Boot Camp , Georgia Institute of Technology SEPTEMBER 2022 – MARCH 2023

Master of Music, Vocal Performance and Opera, Northwestern University, Evanston, IL

Bachelor of Music, Performance, Slippery Rock University of Pennsylvania, Slippery Rock, PA

Graduated summa cum laude with high honors and academic scholarships.